midflorida.com 2010-11-25

# MIDFLORIDA - Support - Privacy

En Espanol  
FAQ  
Glossary  
Legal Policy  
Privacy  
Search  
Site Map  

| 

FACTS | FACTS  | WHAT DOES MIDFLORIDA CREDIT UNION DO WITH YOUR PERSONAL INFORMATION?   
---|---  
  
Why?

| Financial companies choose how they share your personal information. Federal law gives consumers the right to limit some but not all sharing. Federal law also requires us to tell you how we collect, share, and protect your personal information. Please read this notice carefully to understand what we do.  
---|---  
  
What?

|  | The types of personal information we collect and share depend on the product or service you have with us. This information can include:   
---  
  
  * Social Security Number
  * Account Balances
  * Payment History

| 

  * Transaction History
  * Overdraft History
  * Account Transaction

When you are no longer a member, we continue to share your information as described in this notice.   
  
How?

| All financial companies need to share members' personal information to run their everyday business. In the section below, we list the reasons financial companies can share their members' personal information; the reasons MIDFLORDIA Credit Union chooses to share; and whether you can limit this sharing.   
---|---  
Reasons we can share your personal information  | Does MIDFLORIDA Credit   
Union share?  | Can you limit this sharing?   
---|---|---  
**For our everyday business purposes -**  
such as to process your transactions, maintain your   
account(s), respond to court orders and legal   
investigations, or report to credit bureaus  | Yes  | No   
**For our marketing purposes -**  
to offer our products and services to you.  | No  | We don't share   
**For joint marketing with other financial companies** | Yes  | No   
**For our affiliates' everyday business purposes -**  
information about your transactions and experiences  | No  | We don't share   
**For our affiliates' everyday business purposes -**  
information about your creditworthiness  | No | We don't share  
**For nonaffiliates to market to you** | No  | We don't share   
Questions?  | Call toll-free (866) 913-3733   
---|---  
What We Do  
---  
How does MIDFLORIDA Credit Union protect my personal information? | To protect your personal information from unauthorized access and use, we use security measures that comply with federal law. These measures include computer safeguards and secured files and buildings. 

We also maintain other physical, electronic and procedural safeguards to protect this information and we limit access to information to those employees for whom access is appropriate.  
  
How does MIDFLORIDA Credit   
Union collect my personal   
information? |  | We collect your personal information, for example, when you   
---  
  
  * Open an account
  * Apply for a loan
  * Use your credit or debit card

| 

  * Make a wire transfer
  * Make deposits or withdrawals from your account

We also collect your personal information from others, such as credit bureaus, affiliates, or other companies.   
Why can't I limit all sharing? |  | Federal law gives you the right to limit only  
---  
  
  * sharing for affiliates' everyday business purposes - information about your creditworthiness
  * affiliates from using your information to market to you
  * sharing for nonaffiliates to market to you

State laws and individual companies may give you additional rights to limit sharing.  
Definitions  
---  
Affiliates | Companies related by common ownership or control. They can be financial and non-financial companies. 

  * MIDFLORIDA Credit Union does not share with our affiliates.

Nonaffiliates | Companies not related by common ownership or control. They can be financial and non-financial companies. 

  * MIDFLORIDA Credit Union does not share with nonaffiliates so they can market to you.

Joint Marketing | A formal agreement between nonaffiliated financial companies that together market financial products or services to you. 

  * Our joint marketing partners include Securities broker dealers and Insurance companies.

Questions?  | Call toll-free (866) 913-3733   
---|---
